The battle for Earth begins at sea.
Battleship is a thriller, action, adventure film directed by Peter Berg.
When mankind beams a radio signal into space, a reply comes from ‘Planet G’, in the
form of several alien crafts that splash down in the waters off Hawaii.
Lieutenant Alex Hopper is a weapons officer assigned to the USS John Paul Jones, part of an international naval coalition
which becomes the world's last hope for survival as they engage the hostile alien force of unimaginable strength.
While taking on the invaders, Hopper must also try to live up to the potential
that his brother, and his fiancée's father—an Admiral—expect of him.
Lieutenant Alex Hopper, played by Taylor Kitsch.
Commander Stone Hopper, played by Alexander Skarsgård.
Petty Officer Cora 'Weps' Raikes, played by Rihanna.
Sam, played by Brooklyn Decker.
Captain Yugi Nagata, played by Tadanobu Asano.
Cal Zapata, played by Hamish Linklater.
Battleship is a 2012 American military science fiction action film
loosely based on the board game of the same name by Hasbro.
The film was directed by Peter Berg from a script by brothers Jon and Erich Hoeber and stars Taylor Kitsch, Alexander
Skarsgård, Brooklyn Decker, Rihanna in her feature film debut, Tadanobu Asano, Hamish Linklater and Liam Neeson.
Filming took place in Hawaii and on USS Missouri.
In the film, the crews of a small group of warships are forced to battle against a naval
fleet of extraterrestrial origin in order to thwart their destructive goals.
Battleship premiered in Tokyo on April 3, 2012, and was released by
Universal Pictures in the United States on May 18, 2012.
The film received generally negative reviews and underperformed at the box-office, grossing $303 million worldwide
against a production budget of $209–220 million, losing both Universal and Hasbro $150 million.
The film explores themes of fight, u.s. navy, mind
reading, hong kong, football (soccer).
The tone is thought_provoking and intense.